fbpurity.com 2018-02-02

# F.B. Purity - Privacy Policy - Fluff Busting Purity Cleans Your FB Homepage

## Privacy Policy

**Excellatronic Communications** takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

### Routine Information Collection

The F.B. Purity extension/script itself does not record or track any information about your Facebook usage.

This web server (www.fbpurity.com) along with all other web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, Excellatronic Communications uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

### Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

### Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served on this website by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to [opt out of Google's cookie usage](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

### Adware / Spyware / Phishing

F.B. Purity is [completely safe](http://www.fbpurity.com/reviews.htm), and does not install any Adware, Spyware or Toolbars onto your computer, and it also does not ask you for your Facebook username or password.

### Mailing List

If you sign up for The FB Purity News mailing list, your email address will only be used to send you FB Purity related news, it wont be sold or given to any third parties. The mailing list is run via Google's Feedburner service, if you wish to unsubscribe you can do it simply by following the instructions on any email that you receive via the service.

### Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to Steve via the contact form for further clarification.

**Terms and Conditions** : _Use FBP at your own risk, it comes with no warranty or guarantee, neither explicit or implicit towards functionality or usability. The author shall not be held liable for any damage or loss of data caused by use of this program. By downloading and installing Fluff Busting (F.B.) Purity, you agree to these terms._
